我猜你沒有預料到。
I guess you weren't expecting it.
到底是怎麼回事？
What the hell is going on?
我們現在已經到達跳船了。
We have now reached the jump ship.
嗯，估計手術不太順利。
Well, I guess the surgery didn't go so well.
你已經去世了，拉里。
You've passed away, Larry.
你好。
Hello.
我是安娜。我是你來世的四分之一黑格爾。
I'm Anna. I'm your afterlife quarter-neiger.
那不是一份工作。
That's not a job.
這就是交界處，你選擇一個地方度過永恆。
And this is the junction, where you choose one place to spend eternity.
你想吸鼻子嗎？
Do you want a little sniffle?
和誰一起度過？
And who to spend it with?
約翰！約翰！
John! John!
我在那隻眼睛裡很糟糕。
I was in bad in that eye.
你看起來很瘋狂。
You look crazy.
我這是一個令人震驚的消息。
I'm shocking news.
你死定了。
You're dead.
是啊，你怎麼知道？
Yeah, how'd you know?
他花了很長時間才弄清楚這一點。
It took him forever to figure that out.
打擾一下。
Excuse me.
為了這個金鬼，我已經等了67年神債了。
I've been waiting for this Golden Ghost for 67 God-debt years.
我去過。
I've been.
強烈建議使用很多管子來吸進和呼出茶。
A lot of tubes are highly recommended just taking tea breath in and out.
只是呼吸。
Just breathe.
我從來沒有清楚地夢見過耶穌。
I never dreamt Jesus clearly.
正是我夢見你的樣子。
Exactly how I dreamt you.
哦，不。
Oh, no.
這傢伙怎麼樣？
How's this guy?
第一任丈夫。
First husband.
他死於一場戰爭。
He died in a war.
你不擔心嗎？
Don't you worry?
蜂蜜。
Honey.
我知道這很多，但別擔心。
I know this is a lot, but don't worry.
我一直在做研究。
I've been doing the research.
拉里！
Larry!
拉里什麼意思？
What do you mean Larry?
一周前我們在一起了。
We're together a week ago.
那麼，一周內發生了什麼？
Well, what has happened in a week?
你死了。
You died.
我死了。
I died.
我剛剛與我死去的兩個丈夫團聚。
I just been reunited with both of my dead husbands.
我來選擇在哪裡度過永恆。
And I come to pick where to spend eternity.
我來這裡是為了死。
I'm here to die.
你做到了。
You made it.
67年。
67 years.
當永恆都對齊時，似乎什麼都不是。
When eternity's all aligned, seems like nothing.
這是一個很好的開場。
It's a good opening.
你是個潛伏者，朋友。
You're a lurker, pal.
你正在等待破壞半個世紀的婚姻。
You're waiting beyond to spoil a half a century of marriage.
這不是一場比賽。
It's not a competition.
是的。
Yes, it is.
親愛的，這是100%確定的嗎？
Sweetheart, is it 100% for sure?
這是。
It is.
但這不是一場比賽。
But it's not a competition.
這正是我們來這裡的目的。
That's literally what we're here for.
我希望你有自己的生活。
I wanted you to have a life.
但我希望我們也有機會擁有這樣的機會。
But I wanted us to have a chance to have one, too.
他們太浪漫了。
They're so romantic.
我可以很浪漫。
I can be romantic.
好吧，我們到這裡就結束了。
Okay, we're here to end up.
只要我們在一起。
Just as long as we're together.
你必須提醒她看電影愛你。
You're going to have to remind her of watching film loves you.
沒有一個人讓你快樂讓我快樂。
No one you're happy makes me happy.
永恆是一段很長的時間，有遺憾。
Eternity is a long time to have regrets.
所以...
So...
你選擇了你的永恆嗎？
Have you chosen your eternity?